每段关系都都有种模式
Every relationship has its own dynamic.
比如说 我和我妈每晚睡前
For example, my mom and I still like to talk
都会说个不停
every night before bed.
然后小狗找到了我的另一只园丁鞋
And then the dog found my other gardening clog.
我今天的新鲜事就这些了
And that's everything that happened to me today.
一天还没结束呢
And the day's not over yet.
我们来放点莱伊・洛维特的歌然后滚个床单吧
Let's put on some Lyle Lovett and get horizontal.
嗯
Mmm.
好 再见
Okay, Bye.
好恶
Ew.
但是我觉得我永远搞不懂
But I don't think I will ever understand
克洛伊和詹姆斯的奇怪关系
Chloe and James' dynamic.
你今晚油光满面真是太好了
Good thing your face was so oily tonight.
我都能照着你额头补妆
I could check my makeup in your forehead.
你最好补补妆 你看起来像俄亥俄州的
I wish you had. You look like a runner-up
儿童选美大赛亚军
at a child's beauty pageant in ohio.
你看着像刚从傻蛋颁奖仪式上回来
You look like you just got back from the douchie awards
赢了五座傻蛋奖杯
and you won five douchies.
而你只有让说唱歌手摸你才能拿到奖项
Only award You could ever win is for letting rappers touch you.
我不知道你们怎么会这样说话
I don't get how you guys talk to each other like that.
太损了 尤其是在睡前
It's so mean, especially before bedtime.
不损啊 这就是我们
It's not mean. It's just us.
我不知道你穿的是什么鬼东西
And what I don't get is what the hell you're wearing.
噢 是我的中西部早餐睡衣
Oh. They're my midwest breakfast pajamas.
我高中时就有了
I've had them since high school.
我上高中时
When I was in high school,
你已经是个成人 在电视上装嫩装成高中生
you were a grown man pretending to be in high school on tv.
看我在电视里扮演高中生
Watching me pretend to be in high school on TV
是你最像高中生的的时候
was as close to high school as you ever got.
你们让我很不舒服
You are agitating me.
我得再喝一杯甘菊茶才能睡着
I'm gonna need a second cup of chamomile to go to sleep.
喔 放点这个进去
Ooh. Put some of these in there.
保证睡得像死猪一样
You'll sleep like you're dead.
# 我不完美 我也不打小报告 #
I'm not perfect, I'm no snitch
# 但是我可以告诉你 #
but I can tell you
# 她是一个... #
She's a...
# 吧哒哒哒哒吧 吧哒吧 #
Ba-Da-Da-Da-Da-Ba, ba-Da-Ba
23号公寓第二季第十八集 七年损友
阿朱 看看我在地铁上找到的背包
June, Look at this backpack I found on the subway.
我觉得应该是一个小孩的
I think it belongs to a little kid,
但是也有不少好东西
but it's still got good stuff in it.
不好意思 只是在为我的艺术展自拍
Sorry. Just taking a self-Portrait for my art show.
怎么样?
What do you think?
这边
This side,
this side,
还是果照?
or naked?
艺术展么?
Art show?
是的 叫做"糟蹋黄油百种法"
Yep. It's called "Different butter VIOLATIONS."
噢 你想怎么糟蹋黄油呢?
Ooh. How are you gonna violate butter?
希望你摔打人造奶油 我最讨厌人造奶油
I hope you smack around some margarine. I hate margarine.
其实 我在重现一些人糟蹋黄油的情形
Actually, I'm recreating some butter violations
我这些年来做卫生督查时看到过很多
that I've encountered over the years as a health inspector.
你们都会去的吧 是不?
You guys'll be there, right?
当然了 伊莱 我们不会错过...
Of course, Eli. We wouldn't miss...
会有红酒吗?  高档的红酒?
is there gonna be wine? Like, good wine?
要能喝得这么快的红酒?
Like, wine I could drink this fast?
你好 是詹姆斯吗?
Hello. Is James there?
呃... 嗨
Uh... hey.
好消息 明天与艾米丽的早午餐照旧继续
Uh, good news. Brunch with Emily tomorrow is still on.
你确定么?
Are you sure?
我们今早讨论过之后 你还没有丧失兴趣吗?
You haven't lost interest since we talked this morning?
没有 这不是很好嘛 我等不及让你见她了
No. Isn't that great? I can't wait for you to meet her.
她很聪明 乐观积极
She's really smart, positive attitude,
有漂亮的大胸
great breasts.
你知道不?
You know what?
其实应该把"漂亮大胸"放"乐观积极"之前
Actually, "Great breasts" Before "Positive attitude."
你... 你可以脑海里出现那样的画面
You... You should flip those in your mind.
我头发打薄得怎样了?
How's my fade coming?
你的发型不叫打薄
That's not what your haircut's called.
要去见艾米丽 我很兴奋
Well, I'm excited to meet Emily.
我不会穿的过于火辣
I won't rock anything too slutty
因为我不想对她造成威胁
'Cause I don't want to intimidate her.
但是我的确想穿新买的上托胸罩
But I do wanna Wear my new push-up bra,
所以我得考虑一下
so I'm gonna have to figure this out.
我真不相信
I can't believe
詹姆斯一整个月都约同一个女孩出去
James has been seeing the same girl for a month.
他这么喜欢这姑娘 真好呀
It's so sweet that he likes her enough
喜欢到想介绍给我们认识
that he wants to introduce her to us.
我们就像他的父母一样
It's like we're his parents.
或者朋友 阿朱
Or his friends, June.
或只是他的朋友
Or just his friends.
噢 我来过这里 有一次我付钱时支票不够用
Oh, I know this place. I ran out on a check here once.
但没事 那时我带着假发
But it's okay. I was wearing a wig.
别招待她
你们好 欢迎前来
Hey. Thank you for coming.
这就是可爱的艾米丽
This is the lovely Emily.
你一定是克洛伊吧 很高兴认...
You must be Chloe. It's such a pleasure to...
反对
Veto.
噢 很抱歉 我们必须分手
Ohh. I'm sorry. We have to break up.
虽然我们相处得很愉快
This was fun, though.
我... 我不明白 我...
W... I don't... I don't understand. I...
詹姆斯和我有权力反对对方的约会对象
James and I have veto power over whoever the other one dates.
是的 有一人"反对" 另一个人必须遵守
Yeah, if one of us yells "Veto," the other one has to honor it
然后立即结束这段关系
and end the relationship immediately.
你说得真像回事 其实不然
You're saying that like it's a thing, and it is not.
这是一回事 是我们的事 我们一直这样
It is a thing. It's our thing. We've been doing it forever.
克洛伊想要与全国汽车赛冠军杰夫・戈登约会
Ever since Chloe wanted to date nascar champion Jeff Gordon.
反对
Veto.
- 什么?! - 反对!
- What?! - veto!
- 什么?! - 反...
- What?! - ve...
反对!
veto!
但是杰夫・戈登是名人 所以你也不算丢份
But Jeff Gordon is a celebrity, so you're in good company.
永别了
Bye forever.
呃...
Uh...
提醒一句哦
do yourself a favor, though.
一定要再来尝尝这儿的肉桂面包
Come back here sometime and try the cinnamon buns.
非常美味
They're amazing.
你怎么那么快就反对艾米丽
How could you vet Emily so quickly?
你又不了解她
You didn't even know her.
我不需要 这就像超能力一样
I didn't need to. It's like a special power.
有些人有看不见的超能力
Some people have special powers Where they can't see,
有些人有听不到的超能力
and some people have special powers Where they can't hear.
他们是盲人和聋子
Those are blind and deaf people.
他们其实是缺少能力
They're actually lacking powers.
我的能力就是
My special power is,
知道何时詹姆斯的恋情会不了了之
I know when James' relationships are going to end badly.
我不清楚怎么做到的 但是我只要看一眼
I don't know how I do it, but I take one look at the girl
就像"美丽心灵"电影里一样
and it's like I "Beautiful mind" it.
相信我 如果他继续和她约会
And trust me, if he kept going out with her,
他会变得软弱又自满
he'd become soft and complacent.
可怜的女孩啊 你当着她的面就否决了他
That poor girl. You vetoed her right to her face.
她连面包都没吃到
She didn't even get any bread.
阿朱 如果你不对你的朋友
June, if you're not
完全诚实的话
being completely honest with your friends,
那么你就不是在帮忙
then you're not helping them
让他们变得更好
be the best that they can possibly be.
顺便一说
By the way,
你这肤色用错了粉底液
you're using the wrong foundation for your skin tone,
和你的肤色太违和
it actually clashes with your skin tone.
就像你的脸是一个人 脖子是另一个
It's like your face is one girl, and your neck is another.
我刚买了整整一管这东西!
I just bought a whole tub of this stuff!
我不知道 我差点觉得太大比太小更难看
I don't know. I almost think too big is worse than too small.
我明白 这是因为你是男人
I know. That's because you a guy.
相信我 如果你是女人
But trust me, if you're a woman,
太小会让你的鼻子看起来巨大
small just makes your nose look giant.
你们俩还在讨论下半身么?
Are you guys still talking about penises?
不是 我们已经说到墨镜了
No, we've moved on to sunglasses.
是吗?
Did we?
噢 老K来电
Oh. Special k is calling.
她刚才泰国回来 我挂了
She just got back from thailand. I gotta go.
噢 老...
Ooh, spec...
什么事 贱人?
What up, bitch?
不会吧 贱人
Shut up, bitch.
带我一个 贱人
I am in, bitch.
噢!
Ooh!
老K刚刚告诉我有个聚会
Special K just told me about a party
斯派克・李在那大发雷霆
that's happening right now where spike Lee is angry.
詹姆斯一直渴望与他共事
James has been dying to work with him.
我们得赶紧过去
We've gotta go.
噢 天啊! 我爱死他了! 这一定很有趣!
Oh, my god! I love him! This is gonna be so much fun!
我记得"为所应为"里的每一个字
I memorized every word of "do the right thing."
我弄着头发 你给我复述一下
Please recite it to me while I do my hair.
"我给你讲一个左右手的故事"
"Let me tell you a story about the right hand, left hand."
"是关于正义与邪恶的故事
"It is a tale of Good and evil.
仇恨...是凯恩用这只手冰冻了他的兄弟"
Hate--It is with this hand that Cane iced his brother."
带上你那顶软呢帽 詹姆斯!
Grab your least annoying fedora, James!
我们...要见斯派克
We're... going to see spike.
克洛伊 我可以解释的
Chloe. I can explain.
她来这儿干嘛? 我否决了她
What is she doing here? I vetoed her.
是 我...
Yeah, I, uh...
我们还在交往
I didn't end up doing that.
嗨 艾米丽 我是阿朱 我们吃饭的时候见过
Hi, Emily. I'm June. We met at brunch.
"诺比特!"
"Norbit"!
我讨厌这部电影直到我意识到
I hated this movie until I realized
是艾迪・墨菲 这是艾迪・墨菲...
that's Eddie Murphy, that is Eddie Murphy...
你猜怎么着? 是艾迪・墨菲
and guess what? That is Eddie Murphy.
噢 天啊 你们下面还穿着衣服
Oh, my God. You're clothed under there.
给点你们慢慢聊如何?
Why don't I give you guys time to talk?
我去... 餐厅
I'll go stand in the... dining room.
我能看见你们 你们也能看见我
won't be awkward
也不会觉得奇怪
that I can see you, and you can see me.
说吧
Talk.
我...
I...
我...我..我不知道说什么
I-I-I don't know what to say.
她喜欢我本人 而不是电视上的形象吧?
She likes me for me, not the guy on tv. Right, em?
噢 是的 我根本就不知道他上过电视
Oh, it's True. I didn't even know he was on a show.
反对! 我反对你的长相
Ugh, veto! I veto your face.
克洛伊 够了
Chloe, it's done.
你不能只是无视否决权
You can't just override the veto.
或者他可以呢?
Or can he?
詹姆斯又不是第一次无视否决权
This isn't the first time James hasn't honored the veto.
呃!
Ugh!
- 卢瑟! - 抱歉詹姆斯 我忍不住
- Luther! - Sorry, James. I couldn't resist.
克洛伊已经这么对我很多次了
Chloe's shock-Snapped me so many times.
你的松弛机要停产了
Your relaxer got discontinued.
火岛爆炸了
Fire island exploded.
帕蒂・拉贝尔死了
Patti Labelle died.
好了 克洛伊 听我说
All right, Chloe, listen to me.
有时候我的确无视否决权
It's True I haven't always honored the veto,
只是那时我非常非常喜欢那姑娘
but only times when I really, really liked the girl.
或者只是想跟她睡
Or wanted to keep sleeping with her.
这也不行
That doesn't make it okay.
不管怎么说你和那些女孩分手
And you broke up with Those girls anyway,
这说明我否决她们是对的
which means I was right to veto them.
是 最后那些关系都结束了
Yeah. Eventually, those relationships ended,
但是我决定什么时候结束 不是你
but I decided when, not you.
我意思是 你可能有点...
I mean, you can be a little...
嗯 难搞
Mm, difficult.
有时候对你说一套做一套
sometimes it's easier just to tell you one thing
更容易点
and then do something else.
所以你一直都在耍我?
So you've just been humoring me?
不是! 不是
No! No.
好吧...
Well...
我意思是... 是 技术层面上来说
I mean... Yeah, technically.
好 你知道吗? 这段关系完了
Okay, you know what? This isn't gonna work.
克洛伊 听着 我告诉过你
Chloe, listen. I told you.
我是不会和艾米丽分手的
I'm not gonna break up with Emily.
不 我是说你和我 我们结束了
No, I meant you and me. This isn't gonna work.
我想我们该冷静一段时间
I think we should take a break.
也许是的
Maybe we should.
好
Fine.
别等你的事业有难时跑回来找我
But don't come running to me when your career suffers
因为你和她的关系
because your relationship with her
让你变得软弱自满
makes you soft and complacent.
行 你也别等到缺了我不行时
Well, don't you come running back to me when you realize
跑回来找我
how difficult it is to live in a beek-Less world.
变得严重了 我们该怎么办 他们正在分手!
This is serious. We should do something. They're breaking up!
别担心 我来解决
Don't worry. I've got this.
嗨!
Hey!
不!
No!
太慢了 噢
Too slow, ho.
我偷了斯派克・李的棒球帽
I stole spike Lee's baseball hat.
我没有戴 我也不会戴的 但是拿着它很好玩
I'm not wearing it. I won't wear it. But it's fun to hold.
把你的钥匙给我 我把他们放帽子里
Give me your keys. I'll put 'em in there.
我不敢相信你和詹姆斯分手后
I can't believe you went to that party
又去了那个聚会
after you and James broke up.
你们做朋友七年了
You guys have been friends for seven years.
这不是小事
It is a big deal.
这是事实 友谊结束了
It happens. Friendships die.
帽子被偷了 钥匙在里面
Hats get stolen. Keys go in them.
好吧 你可以假装不在乎 但我不能
Well, you can pretend you don't care, but I can't.
你们俩对我来说都很重要
You both mean a lot to me,
我不会选择任何一方的
and I am not going to choose sides.
我父母离婚时我犹豫了一星期
I did that one weekend when my parents split up.
我选了我爸爸...
I chose my dad--
阿朱 就不能乘你和詹姆斯出去的时候
June, can you save this awesome story
再讲这精彩故事么? 谢谢
for when you're hanging out with James? Thanks.
女士们好
Hello, ladies.
不要听到"那个男的"
Not to sound like "That guy,"
不过我的艺术展的传单做好啦
but my art show Flyers are ready.
太好了! 我好激动 我爱黄油
Cool! I'm excited. I love butter.
为什么? 因为你从那些成立胆固醇食品组
Why? Because you're from one of those states
的那些州来吗?
where Cholesterol's a food group?
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
你们那儿的人是直接从搅拌机里吃
Do your people eat straight from the churn
还是用盘子吃东西?
or do they use plates?
克洛伊 我不和你互相损
Chloe, I'm not doing this mean thing with you.
你家人的膝盖是原装的?
Does anyone in your family have their original knees?
噢 天啊 我不知道是过敏还是什么
Oh, god, I don't know if it's allergies or what,
眼睛里进了东西
but there's something in there.
噢 算了吧! 你在这方面很不擅长!
Oh, forget it! You're terrible at this!
你好 詹姆斯的前任朋友
Hello, former friend of James.
我把你留在他那儿的所有东西
I have taken the liberty of returning all the possessions
都送来了
you left at his place.
你的手铐 咕咕娃音碟...
Your handcuffs, a goo goo dolls cd...
另一个咕咕娃音碟
another Goo Goo dolls cd,
还有一张去特德・丹森家的地图
and a map to Ted Danson's house.
好极了 因为我也把他留在这儿的
Great, because I also put together
东西装了起来
a box of things that James left here.
奇怪 我有和那一样的抓痒器
That is weird. I have that same back scratcher.
这是我的小狗梅齐的照片!
And that is a photo of my dog Maisie!
- 这是我的东西! - 被你发现了 嗯?
- This is my stuff! - Oh, you caught that, huh?
我本来要说 詹姆斯已经有两个抓痒器了
I was gonna say, James already has two back scratchers.
你们正看着呢
You're looking at 'em.
嗯!
Mmm!
真是太好了 还没有人在这个厨房做过饭
It's amazing. Nobody has ever cooked in this kitchen before.
他一直把钱放在烤箱里
He was keeping money in the oven.
哈! 我只是觉得
Ha! I just think it's great
我能和你还有克洛伊做朋友真是太好了
that I can be friends with both you and Chloe.
我会完全保持中立的 知道吗?
I'm gonna be totally neutral, you know?
我不会再选爸爸了
I'm not picking my dad again.
嗯 你好像有话要说 阿朱
Well, sounds like there's a story here, June.
还是别说了
Let's blow past it.
哦
Oh.
我不会选任何一方 但我觉得你和克洛伊...
I'm not picking sides, but I do think that you and Chloe shou--
我... 我希望你别说了
I'm--I'm gonna stop you right there.
我一点都不想听到克洛伊的事
I don't need to hear anything about Chloe.
我很清楚接下来会怎样
I know exactly what's gonna happen.
下次她在满是青年人的俱乐部里
The next time she projectile vomits
乱扔东西随处呕吐时
in a club full of 20-Somethings,
不会再来让我付清洁费啦
she's not gonna have me to pay the dry cleaning bill.
好吧 她是不会真的到处扔东西呕吐的...
Okay, she didn't really projectile Vomit all over--
- 上周三 - 上个月两次了
- last wednesday. - Twice last month.
- 看见你分享的昨晚和詹姆斯
- Saw the pictures of your dinner with James
吃饭时的照片了 - 很愉快呢
on Instagram last night. - Oh, yeah, it was fun.
是 看起来不错
Yeah, it looked like it.
你看到我传的照片了吗?
Uh, did you see the pictures I posted?
- 不 没看到 - 哦对了! 我没传照片
- No, I didn't. - Oh, right! I didn't post any pictures,
因为我一个人在家
because I was home alone
看蛇类纪录片
watching a documentary about snakes.
大家好 这是贝克特・埃弗雷特
All, this is Beckett Everett.
他名字里有两个特
He's got four t's in his name,
他刚参演了三集"高校利齿"
he just did a three-Episode arc on "High school Fangs."
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 你是新奥尔良十九世纪闪回季
Oh, my God. You were the best part
最精彩的部分
of the new Orleans 1800s flashback season.
的确是 他是第二个詹姆斯・范德・比克
Yes, he was. He's the next James Van der beek,
但他会比他更出名很优秀
only he's gonna be even huger and Better.
他的头部的比例比詹姆斯当年要匀称
His head is better proportioned than James' was at that age.
克洛伊 你不能找人替代詹姆斯
Chloe, you can't replace James.
是的 我可以
Yes, I can.
我换了我的鞋子 换了我的狗
I replaced my shoes, I replaced my dog,
在你没落地生根前
I replaced my roommate
我还换了我的室友呢
until you put down roots of steel.
超人是根骨惊奇
Superman was the man of steel.
这话真突兀 你为什么要这样说?
That was random. Why would you say that?
你的帅气把你脑子堵住了吗?
Did your handsomeness just Leak into your brain?
会发生这种事吗?
Can that happen?
天啊!
Ugh! God!
为什么每个人都不会损人?
Why is everyone So bad at this?
你能给我两百美元让我付话费吗?
Can I have $200 to pay my cell phone bill?
我最近老是打恶作剧电话给凯莉・奥斯本
I've been been prank calling Kelly Osbourne more than usual.
我可没两百美元
I don't have $200.
我只拍了三集"高校利齿"
I've only done, like, three episodes of "H.S.F.,"
我还要养我的母亲
and I'm supporting my mom.
她同时也是我的经纪人
She's also my manager.
我叫她"妈妈经"
I call her my "Momager."
谢谢
Thank you.
克洛伊 是我
Hey Chloe, it's me.
我猜你已经交了话费了
I guess you paid your bill,
因为我能给你留言了
because I'm leaving you this message.
我只想问问你还好吗
Just wanted to make sure you're okay,
因为我从昨天开始就没见过你
because I haven't seen you since yesterday
自从你甩开贝克特・埃弗雷特之后
when you stormed out on Beckett Everett...
他名字里有七个字呢
who also has five "E's" in his name.
别人都没注意到
No one else noticed it.
不管怎么样 打给我
Anyway, call me.
卢瑟
Luther.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我看到了些东西 我十分矛盾
I've seen something, and I'm conflicted.
我不知道该怎么做或怎么感受
I don't know what to do or how to feel.
我...你要进来吗?
I... do you want to come in?
我不...
I don't...
想
think so.
你至少把外套脱了吧?
Do you at least want to take off your coat?
不
No.
天啊
Oh, god.
克洛伊出什么事了吗?
Did something happen to Chloe?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
她和詹姆斯绝交之后发疯了??
Did she spiral out without James?
她进监狱了? 她死了吗?
Is she in jail? Is she dead?
她死在大马路上了?
Is she dead in the street?
不
Unh-Unh.
我.. 我只是...
I... I just...
我不...
I don't...
克洛伊找了份工作
Chloe has a job
在闪闪手机店上班?
working at gloss mobile?
太糟糕了
It's awful.
但是也...
But also...
有点搞笑
kind of funny.
就像一个龙卷风袭击了一个香蕉工厂
Like a tornado ripping through a banana factory.
我在视频网上看到的
I saw it on youtube.
人和香蕉
People and bananas,
转啊转...
swirling and swirling...
真悲哀
It's sad.
她在干嘛? 快点
What is she doing? Come on.
- 我们得进去和她谈谈 - 不
- We gotta go in and talk to her. - Mnh-Mnh.
我要先理清思绪再行动
I don't act until I know how I feel.
当我试图把自己丢进我妈的棺材里
I learned that lesson when I tried to throw myself
我才得到这个教训
into my mother's Coffin. Mm.
克洛伊?
Chloe?
呃... 你...
Um... do you...
在闪闪手机店上班?
work here at... at... gloss Mobile?
抱歉 你得拿个预约号
I'm sorry. You're gonna have to take a number.
但是... 这里没人
But... there's no one else around.
拿号码 女士
Number, ma'am.
九号!
9!
十号!
10!
十号?
10?
- 十一号! - 我是十一号
- 11! - I'm 11.
你好 欢迎光临闪闪手机店
Hi. Welcome to gloss mobile.
请问我能帮您什么吗
How can I help you?
你想为你的手机设备加个配饰吗?
Are you interested in an accessory for your device today?
克洛伊
Chloe,
你在这里干嘛?
what are you doing here?
我不知道 我过来付话费
I don't know. I came in to pay my bill,
然后我因为通话累计市场去了客服中心
and I got into it with customer service about rollover minutes,
之后我就在这儿上班了
and the next thing you know I was working here.
是因为...你需要钱吗
Is this because... You need money
自从你和詹姆斯...
since you and James...
阿朱 这和钱没任何关系
June, this has nothing to do with money.
弄钱的办法我多得是
I have plenty of scams to generate money.
我在这里是因为... 我热爱这儿
I'm here because...  I love it.
你叫十号了吗?
Um, did you call 10?
叫了两次 我已经跳到十一号了
Twice. I've moved on to 11.
你应该待在附近的
You're supposed to stay within the vicinity.
我就站在这里
I was standing right over there.
我没有听到你叫十号
I didn't hear you call 10.
真神奇啊你是十
Ironic that you'd be a 10,
你明显只值两分
seeing as how you're clearly a 2.
对于一个有刘海的成年女性 你真有自信
You're awfully confident for a grown woman with Bangs.
让我猜猜你为什么会在这儿
Let me guess why you're here.
是不是当你在爱抚你的香肠和葡萄时
You dropped your phone in the toilet
把手机掉马桶里了?
while caressing your hot dog and grapes?
这两个食物根本不应该放一起
Ew. Those foods don't even go together.
我要交换载体
I'm gonna switch carriers.
哈! 祝你好运
Ha! Good luck with that.
回去看看你的合同 这是归我们的
Check your contract. We own your ass.
啊 真满足
Ahh. So satisfying.
克洛伊 我想我知道这是为什么了
Chloe, I think I know what's happening here.
你和客人对骂
You are trading insults with customers
是因为你想念和詹姆斯对骂的感觉
because you miss doing that with James.
不 我知道这看起来不像我
No. I know it doesn't seem like me.
但我真的认为我找到了合适我的工作
But I really think I found my niche--
我在培训中学到这个词的
I learned that word in training.
我爱闪闪手机店
I love glo-Mo.
我这个礼拜要求上九十小时的班
I signed up for 90 hours this week.
我想要上更多
I tried to sign up for more,
但显然 他们也只开那么久
but apparently, that's all they're open.
怪不得中国人要超越我们了
I mean, no wonder the Chinese are beating us.
十二号!
12!
我是十二号到二十五号
I'm numbers 12 through 25.
我有很多问题
I have a lot of questions.
等等 奇怪了
Wait, I'm confused.
克洛伊有了工作不应该是件好事吗?
Isn't it a good thing that Chloe has a job?
她显然很伤心
She's clearly hurting.
克洛伊不是那种拿薪水的人
Chloe isn't the kind of person who gets a paycheck,
也不是那种中午会用微波炉加热东西的人
or who heats things up in the microwave at lunch.
这些事
This is the kind of thing
是她全力避免的
that she spent her whole life trying to avoid.
她人生到了谷底
This is her rock bottom.
你以一个非常戏剧化的方式
You're describing really normal things
描述了非常平常的事
in a really dramatic way.
她穿着褶裥裤
She was wearing pleated pants.
还有她的鞋子
And her shoes...
天哪 她的鞋...
my god, her shoes...
畸形 纯黑 一如黑夜般死板
orthopedics. Solid black. Dead as night.
你知道这是什么吗?
You know what this is?
是没了詹姆斯的克洛伊
This is Chloe in a beek-Less world.
伊莱 你好吗?
Eli. Are you okay?
我看到了...
I've seen something...
我刚在艺术展 你们都迟到了
I was at my art show, which you're all late for, by the way.
我看见了...
I saw it, and...
我不得不来找你们 我...
I had to leave and come find you. I just...
我也不知道
I don't know.
嘿 朋友们
Hey guys.
我的天啊 詹姆斯成了个大肥仔
Oh, my. James is a giant Peach.
没错 我知道
Yes, I know.
我... 自从上次见面后我胖了一点
I... put on a little weight since the last time I saw you.
我两天前刚和你吃过饭
I just had dinner with you two days ago.
是的 我... 我胖起来略快
Yeah. I'm... I'm a quick fat.
我开心的时候 就会像这样胖起来
When I'm happy, I tend to put on weight like that.
但没关系 艾米丽不介意
But it's okay. Emily doesn't mind.
是吗 小艾 让他们看看你怎么摸我肚子的
No. Right, Em? Show them how you rub my belly.
我觉得他很可爱
Oh, I think he's adorable.
他是我的圆滚滚胖小子
He's my jiggly wiggly jigglepuss.
- 我去拿些芝士块 - 好
- I'll get some cheese cubes. - All right.
告诉你们
Ahh! I tell you,
我觉得我和艾米丽在一起太舒服了
I just feel so comfortable with Emily, with myself.
我...
It just...
做自己的感觉真棒
I just feel good in my own body.
但是 詹姆斯...
But, James...
你是个演员
Y-You're an actor.
你不... 不担心自己的演艺生涯吗
Aren't... aren't you worried about your career?
当然不是 许多优秀的演员都有过体重问题
Nah. Many fine actors have had dramatic weight gains
但也都没影响工作
and just kept right on Working.
方・基默
Uh, Val Kilmer,
文斯・沃恩 史蒂芬・席格
Vince Vaughn, Steven seagal.
我觉得这三个人都胖得无法直视
I find all three of those people hard to look at.
这里是属于伊莱和他的展品的 别光顾着聊我
Anyway, this isn't about me. This is about Eli and his show.
是不? 你看这!
Right? I mean, look at this!
詹姆斯是在分散自己的注意力
James is voluntarily deflecting attention from himself.
他的人生也到了谷底
This is his rock bottom.
那一定是伊莱的妈妈
That has got to be Eli's mother.
简直就是穿裙子的伊莱
It's Eli in a dress.
抱歉 我来晚了
Hey. Sorry, I'm late.
我不能提早下班
I couldn't leave work early
因为经理拉杰这人实在太难搞
because my manager raj is being a real hard ass.
不过我还挺尊敬他
but I respect him.
快看 他们又在一起了
Look. They're back together.
他们意识到没有了彼此 自己就一团糟
They realized what a mess they are without each other
他们会好好谈谈的
and they're gonna talk.
你的尼龙扣弯了
Your velcro's crooked.
谢谢
Thanks.
你长白头发了
You've got frosting in your hair.
噢 我之前就开始长了
Oh. I-I had frosting earlier.
这就结束了?
That's it?
不会吧
That can't be it.
算了 我等不了了
You know what? I'm done.
我不会傻站在这
I'm not gonna stand back here
看着他们抛弃这段美好的友情
and watch them throw away this beautiful friendship.
我再也不玩中立了
No more being neutral.
我选我的妈妈和爸爸
I choose mom and Dad.
嘿 听着
Hey, look.
你们是朋友
You guys are friends,
所以你们得表现得像一对朋友
so you should be acting like it.
看看你们俩!
I mean, look at each other!
克洛伊 你应该说些什么...
Chloe, you should say something...
比如 说他胖
I don't know, like, fat to him.
然后是你 詹姆斯 你也应该说些什么
And then, James, you should say something
说闪闪手机店有多逊
about how lame gloss mobile is.
然后 克洛伊 你会说"是吗?
Then, Chloe, You'll be all like, "Well, you know what?
你真是胖得超乎想象"
You're even fatter than I said you were before."
然后詹姆斯会说"是吗?
And then James will be all like, "Well, you know what?
我至少跑得比闪闪店的数据传输要快"
I'm faster than glo-Mo data transfers."
克洛伊又会说"那你对与布莱恩・丹内利
And then Chloe will be like, "Well, what is it like
争夺同一个角色有何感想?"
competing against Brian Dennehy for roles?"
詹姆斯又会说"那你和蕾丝们比谁穿衬衫
and then James will be all like, "Oh, well, what is it like
漂亮又感觉如何"
competing against lesbians For shirts?"
你来我往! 互相羞辱! 扯皮! 嘲笑!
Back and forth! Insults! Tears! Laughter!
最好再抱抱?
Hugging?
没错! 他们抱了起来!
Yes! They're hugging!
她的屁股上沾了黄油
She's got butter on her Butt.
黄油屁股
Butter Butt.
我... 噢 天哪 我刚靠在了伊莱的墙上
I... Oh, god. I was standing against Eli's wall.
她想把它擦掉 却弄到了毛衣上
She's trying to wipe it off. She's got it on her sweater.
毛衣黄油 卢瑟也来了
Sweater butter. Oh, now Luther's gettin' in there.
- 黄油擦屁者 - 黄油擦屁者
- Butter Butt rubber. - Butter Butt rubber.
行了 过来吧
Okay, come on.
确实 我过得不太好
Obviously, I'm not doing so well.
是啊
Yeah.
我也一样
Me, neither.
这颈笔不错
Nice neck pen.
至少我有个脖子能挂着
At least I have a neck.
我挺怀念这一切
I've missed this.
你是对的 我变得柔弱而又自满
You're right. I got soft and complacent
没你在我没那么犀利了
without you around to keep me sharp.
我也不想过没有你的日子
I don't wanna live in a beek-Less world.
实在太可怕了
It's too gruesome.
昨天我还填一个叫w-2表格
Yesterday, I had to fill out something called a w-2 form.
每一栏我填的都是"球"
I mean, I wrote the word "Balls" In every section,
但...也得写那么多蛋呢
but still... I had to fill it out.
这是什么?
What is this?
别再戴了
Get rid of this.
抱歉 你戴着吧
Excuse me. There you go.
能给我一杯香槟吗 麻烦你了 谢谢?
Can I have a glass of Champagne, please? Thanks.
别再无视我的否决了
Don't ever blow off my veto again.
我觉得我们还是别再玩什么一票否决了
I say we just veto the vetoes.
好吧 可以 因为杰夫・戈登联系我了
Okay, good, because Jeff Gordon called.
他开车绕完五百圈
He's driving 500 times in a circle
要来找我约会
and then he wants to hang out.
你们终于复合了!
Oh, you guys made up!
耶! 我又拯救一段感情
Yay! I saved another relationship.
当我让我爸妈重归于好的时候...
You know, when I got my mom and dad back together...
这恐龙是由腐臭的黄油做的
You weren't standing 10 feet
你们有本事站这么远
from a dinosaur made of rancid butter,
你们有本事看一眼啊
which you haven't even looked at yet.
你们谁都没看过
None of you have looked at it.
还不快看!
Look at it!
运气不错 你瘦得也略快
you're lucky you're a quick thin.
是啊 但过程挺艰辛的
I know. That got rough.
之前洗澡的时候连鸡巴都看不到了
I was having trouble seeing my Dong in the shower.
说得好像以前看得到似的
It's always kind of been hard to see.
是吗 艾米丽?
Right, Emily?
艾米丽
Emily.
抱歉 我们聊得太投入了
I'm so sorry. We got off-Track there.
说实话
Uh, listen.
我们是不会有结果的
It's not gonna work out between us.
和你在一起我变得太胖了
I got fat on your watch.
但... 詹姆斯 我不懂
But... James, I don't understand.
不管你变成什么样 我都喜欢你
I like you no matter what you look like.
- 是的 这就是问题所在 - 是的
- Yeah, that's the problem. - Yeah, see,
我需要的是一个有条件地爱我的人
I'm looking for someone to give me conditional love.
已经有人无条件地爱我了
I already have someone who gives me unconditional love.
说的就是我
That's me.
全脂牛奶? 我说...
Full-Fat milk? I mean...
否决 我否决卢瑟
veto! I veto Luther.